Intro with the swords and make it really impressive right? Oh lordy ah I can't be
only one and I killed the other one on the internet nobody has good taste so it
would become a meme I'm sure. Is this you approving that we can do that then? Oh yeah
absolutely if I'm dead I won't care. Okay speaking of you're dead and won't be able
to I guess consent to it. What necrophilia now? No no I'm sorry it's not where I was going.
I was going to go into the topic about AI and generative AI is it a bubble or is it a computing
revolution? I mean it's clearly both right it's clearly a bubble and at the same time it's very
interesting and I think it will change society and I think it will change how most skilled jobs get
done at the same time I don't think it's as revolutionary as people make it out to be. I
want to specifically talk about AI with respect to coding and particularly vibe coding what are
your thoughts on an AI model being trained on the work of real people like in the artistic
community rightfully angry that the AI never would have been able to do anything without the
large-scale theft of work so what is your take on on that? I'm like that's reality deal with it
that genie is out of the bottle you're not you're not getting it back and you're not getting it back
whether you are a photographer who's out of work those things are gone right because you can fake
pictures so much better now or you're a programmer that has to learn to deal with a new reality. I
think actually on the programming side we're in a fairly good spot I really think that AI will be
a tool and it will make people more productive I think that by coding is great for getting into
programming I think it's gonna be a horrible thing to maintain right oh yeah right so I don't think
programmers go away you still want to have the people who know how to maintain the end result
I'm a huge believer in AI I'm not a huge believer in the the whole things going on around AI I find
the market marketing and the market to be sick and twisted and and there is going to be a crash
and it's not it's going to be ugly not financial advice no no no financial advice speaking of